A Guide to the Books That Made the Difference Project Collection, 1980-1986
Special Collections, Virginia Polytechnic Institute and State University
- Cassette Tapes 56-75. (Box 7)
  - Tape 74
    "All Things Considered," National Public Radio, March, 1981. Susan Stamberg reads letters in answer to request for listeners to write in about significant books.
  - Tape 75
    "Virginia Bookshelf"—Gordon and Patricia Sabine interviewed by Seth Williamson, 1981?